<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Wuthering Waves Articles</title>
    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
    <link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/TheLovinator1/wutheringwaves/refs/heads/master/articles_latest.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
    <id>urn:wutheringwaves:feed</id>
    <updated>2026-01-07T11:27:58+00:00</updated>
    <subtitle>Latest articles from Wuthering Waves</subtitle>
    <icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/TheLovinator1/wutheringwaves/refs/heads/master/logo.png</icon>
    <logo>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/TheLovinator1/wutheringwaves/refs/heads/master/logo.png</logo>
    <rights>Copyright © 2026 Wuthering Waves</rights>
    <generator uri="https://git.lovinator.space/TheLovinator/wutheringwaves" version="1.0">Python Script</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
    </author>
    
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3962</id>
                    <title>[Bountiful Crescendo] Limited-Time Material Double Drop Event</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3962" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1767715200000/xm3ojhoidz1utkw2nx-1767756441883.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1767715200000/kmlzix5o9l8dbgjm0q-1767756461735.jpg" /></p>
<p>The Sonoro Spheres are undergoing an accelerating collapse due to the Waveworn Phenomenon. However, this is also intensifying the energy within, resulting in more valuable materials.</p>
<p>Use the Waveplates to maximize your rewards from the Remnant Crystals.</p>
<h1>Duration</h1>
<p>2026-01-08 04:00 - 2026-01-15 03:59 (server time)</p>
<h1>Eligibility</h1>
<p>Reach Union Level 14.</p>
<h1>Details</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Complete Simulation Challenge and Forgery Challenges during the event and spend Waveplates for double rewards.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Simulation Challenge and Forgery Challenge share the double rewards claims.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>During [Bountiful Crescendo], you can claim double rewards 3 times a day, and the remaining double rewards claims can be viewed on the [Bountiful Crescendo] event page.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>During [Bountiful Crescendo], double rewards claims refresh daily at 04:00 (server time).</p>
</li>
</ul>]]></content>
                    <published>2026-01-07T11:27:58+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2026-01-07T11:27:58+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3956</id>
                    <title>Post-Lament Anthropocene: Enemies — Hyvatia</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3956" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hyvatia is Spacetrek Collective&#39;s first detection array built at Sundermere to monitor and stabilize the Reactor Drive&#39;s energy state in real time.</p>
<p>The Research Institute implanted the Exostrider&#39;s space-time error correction module runtime into Hyvatia&#39;s core, allowing Hyvatia to adjust the Exostrider&#39;s orbit and detect hidden spaceborne threats with high precision. Therefore, Hyvatia possesses sufficient computational power to predict the Reactor Drive&#39;s rotation.</p>
<p>Hyvatia&#39;s core function is to detect abnormal or dangerous energy fluctuations, perform immediate emergency calibrations, and feed this data back to the Drive to ensure stable operation.<img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1767542400000/nhzo07ndoetofjec5w-1767579707949.jpg" /></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1767542400000/ghib6yf059dfnmxw8y-1767579724544.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1767542400000/thr3q4oc0lhbsvg30f-1767579772974.gif" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1767542400000/sig4encw9xux7erba4-1767579786069.gif" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1767542400000/0trgexzpmm387lvhqb-1767579812153.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1767542400000/mzz2bxpjvhp8os8l5a-1767579828396.gif" /></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2026-01-05T10:24:42+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2026-01-05T10:24:42+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3946</id>
                    <title>[Beyond the Waves: Lahai-Roi] Featured Exploration Event</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3946" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1767024000000/tye6hmfqtxk4ttgexk-1767068208964.jpg" /></p>
<p>To encourage the Pioneers to further share their Lahai-Roi explorations, Lollo Logistics has partnered with the Pioneer Association to proudly present the campaign: Beyond the Waves!</p>
<p>Participate and upload your Adventure Logs to the Lollo courier truck to get various Adventure Packages!</p>
<h1>Duration</h1>
<p>2026-01-01 04:00 - 2026-01-19 03:59 (server time)</p>
<h1>Rewards</h1>
<p>Astrite x400, Lustrous Tide x5, Premium Enclosure Tank - Lahai-Roi x20, Premium Tuner x90, Crystal Solvent x6, Shell Credit x420000, and other Materials.</p>
<h1>Eligibility</h1>
<p>Reach Union Level 14 and activate the Resonance Nexus in Startorch Academy during Main Quest Chapter III Act I &#34;&#34;What Burns Beneath Frostlands.&#34;&#34;</p>
<h1>Event Details</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>During the event, you can complete event objectives once per day to obtain a set number of Adventure Logs. Each Adventure Log can be exchanged for an Adventure Package.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Adventure Packages contain special mechanics that, when triggered, unlock a large amount of rewards.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>There are 3 Inventories for the Adventure Packages. Once you collect all deliveries in an Inventory, the next Inventory will be unlocked.</p>
</li>
</ul>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-30T12:17:09+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-30T12:17:09+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3941</id>
                    <title>Wuthering Waves V3.0 Short-form Video Creative Event is officially live!</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3941" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Dear Rovers,</p>
<p>The Wuthering Waves V3.0 Short-form Video Creative Event is officially live! To participate, publish a short-form video that complies with the event rules on YouTube Shorts, Instagram, or TikTok, with hashtags #WutheringWaves, #wuwacreator and #wuwashorts included. There are no restrictions on content type or format. Creators who submit valid entries will qualify to share a prize pool and compete for cash rewards of up to $2,400, along with additional Astrites rewards.</p>
<p>Submission Form Link: &lt;https://forms.gle/fiJAhMXGr2Bz3M2v6&gt;</p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766678400000/ev71v0a0ne78617kk4-1766746858407.jpg" /></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-26T12:39:28+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-26T12:39:28+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3936</id>
                    <title>V3.0 WUWA Discord Quest Livestream Event Begins!</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3936" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766678400000/hzzi0vb6nknb7nz2yj-1766718595835.jpg" />Dear Rover,</p>
<p>V3.0 WUWA Discord Quest Livestream Event has begun. Click the link below to complete the streaming quest on Discord and get a chance to win rewards including Morphable Echo!</p>
<p>&lt;https://discord.com/quests/1448749066774380766&gt;</p>
<h2>Event Duration</h2>
<p>2025/12/26 ~ 2025/12/31 17:00 (PT)</p>
<h2>Rewards</h2>
<p>Shell Credit* 20,000</p>
<p>Advanced Resonance Potion* 3</p>
<p>Advanced Energy Core* 3</p>
<p>Astrite* 30</p>
<p><strong>Please</strong> <strong>note that the rewards are limited to 300,000 in total and will be given out on a first-come, first-served basis, determined by the time the Redemption Code is claimed after completing the streaming quest.</strong> <strong>The Redemption Code will expire at 2026/02/05 at 15:59 (PT). The reward will be limited to one reward redemption per account.</strong></p>
<h2>Who is Eligible</h2>
<p>Available to players on PC where both Discord and Wuthering Waves are available. Discord’s premium services are restricted in some regions.</p>
<h2><strong>Other Terms</strong></h2>
<p>Limit of one reward redemption per account. For more information on Discord Quests, please visit <a href="https://support.discord.com/hc/articles/22225719947543">Discord Quest Help Center</a>.</p>
<h2>How to Participate</h2>
<p>In order to successfully complete the <strong>V3.0 WUWA Discord Quest</strong>, players who meet the eligibility criteria must live stream their <strong>Wuthering Waves</strong> gameplay to a friend via a Discord voice channel for a minimum duration of 15 minutes on the desktop app.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Before you can begin the Quest, launch the game.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Then, head to your Discord desktop app and navigate to a direct message (DM), group chat, or a server of your choice.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Once there, start a voice call or join a voice channel and select the <strong>Screen</strong> <strong>Share</strong> icon located in the voice status panel. Be sure to select the individual application for the game before you Go Live.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>NOTE: You must select the game application to stream! Streaming your device’s screen will not progress your Quest forward. Once you stream, you can check the progress bar on the Quest Home to ensure progress is being made on the Quest.</li>
</ul>
<ol start="4">
<li>When you’re ready to stream your gameplay, press <strong>Go Live.</strong> You can learn more about streaming your game <a href="https://support.discord.com/hc/en-us/articles/360040816151-Go-Live-and-Screen-Share#h_01HFFJ28PJAY9AHGRQ85XRSF8G">here</a>.</li>
</ol>
<h2>Redemption Instructions</h2>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Once you have completed the Quest by streaming 15 minutes of Wuthering Waves, you will receive a reward code in Quest Home (Discovery &gt; Quests). For detailed instructions on how to claim your reward code, please refer to our <a href="https://support.discord.com/hc/articles/22225719947543-Discord-Quests-FAQ#h_01HVPBZR5FKKSQ3R1JXB9E4DM3">Discord Quests FAQ</a>.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Select your server and enter Wuthering Waves, and then go to [Settings] - [Other] - [Redemption Code].</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Enter the [Redemption Code] and hit [Confirm] to redeem rewards. You can then claim them in your in-game mail.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The [Redemption Code] function will be unlocked once you&#39;ve reached Union Level 2.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Redemption Code obtained in this event will expire on 2026/02/05 at 15:59 (PT). Redemption Codes that expire will be unable to be redeemed.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<h2>Discord Quest FAQ</h2>
<p><strong>Q: Is there a limit on how many Quests I can redeem on my Discord account?</strong></p>
<p>A: Eligible users can redeem one of each of the available Quest campaigns on their Discord account.</p>
<p>For more information on Discord Quests, visit our <a href="https://support.discord.com/hc/articles/22225719947543">Discord Quest Help Center</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Q: Is this feature/promotion available in my region?</strong></p>
<p>A: Some Quests will not be available in all regions based on terms and conditions. If you are in an ineligible region for a Quest, you will not be able to complete it.</p>
<p>Additionally, Discord’s premium services are restricted in some regions. If you are unable to access the Gift Inventory, you are not eligible for Quests.</p>
<p><strong>Q: I have concerns or questions regarding privacy and Quests.</strong></p>
<p>A: We encourage you to review <a href="https://discord.com/privacy">Discord’s Privacy Policy</a> for further details about how we use your information. You can head over to our <a href="https://support.discord.com/hc/en-us/articles/22225542459415">Data Used for In-Game Rewards</a> article, to learn more about how we use data for Quests.</p>
<p><strong>Q: Why am I unable to complete Quest while using Linux?</strong></p>
<p>A: Currently, Quest rewards are unable to be earned on Linux devices.</p>
<p>However, Discord team is looking into a resolution for this issue so that earning Quest rewards is possible on Linux in the future. For now, we recommend completing the requirement on a different operating system, like Windows or MacOS.</p>
<p>Discord support team does not have an exact ETA for when a solution will be available, and won&#39;t be able to provide any status updates on this specific issue.</p>
<p><strong>Q: I no longer see a Quest. Where did it go?</strong></p>
<p>A: Quests are typically only available for a limited amount of time. If you no longer see a Quest in the Quest Home or in-app notifications about the quest, the period to complete and claim the reward for the Quest is over.</p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-26T11:10:52+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-26T11:10:52+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3930</id>
                    <title>Wuthering Waves Fan Creation Event &#34;We Who See the Stars&#34; is now live!</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3930" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/fqjug7j4a4946z4u9l-1766635651621.jpg" />Dear Rovers,</p>
<p>Wuthering Waves Fan Creation Event &#34;We Who See the Stars&#34; is now live! Post your work with hashtags #WutheringWaves and #WuWaFanart on X (Twitter)/Instagram/Facebook and fill out the form for a chance to win iPhone 16 Pro 512GB, Astrites and more!</p>
<p>Create your works of boundless imagination to present the world of Wuthering Waves!</p>
<p>Proceed to submit: &lt;https://forms.gle/7nvwpMB75oqQUaBK8&gt;</p>
<p>Content Requirement</p>
<p>Create your own artwork about Wuthering Waves Version 3.0 &#34;We Who See the Stars&#34;!</p>
<p>Whether it&#39;s an illustration of your beloved character, comical moments from your adventures, or difficult combos you&#39;ve mastered—anything that aligns with the theme is eligible for submission. Share your artwork or video for a chance to win exciting prizes!</p>
<p>How to Submit</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Post your artwork on X (Twitter)/Instagram/Facebook with both hashtags #WutheringWaves and #WuWaFanart included.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Complete the submission form with your submission details. Once done, your submission will be considered successful.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>Please quote your post link with the right hashtags published publicly on the designated platforms.</li>
</ul>
<p>Submission form: &lt;https://forms.gle/7nvwpMB75oqQUaBK8&gt;</p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/3ior3r15mo14okh1un-1766635712232.jpg" /></p>
<p>Submission Period</p>
<p>2025/11/20 - 2025/12/14 (PT)</p>
<p>Rewards</p>
<p>1st Place (5 Winners): iPhone 17 Pro 512GB</p>
<p>2nd Place (5 Winners): 6,000 Astrites &amp; 800 USD</p>
<p>3rd Place (10 Winners): 3,000 Astrites &amp; 400 USD</p>
<p>4th Place (15 Winners): 2,000 Astrites &amp; 200 USD</p>
<p>5th Place (20 Winners): 1,000 Astrites &amp; $50 Amazon Gift Card</p>
<p>Lucky Prize (20 Winners): $20 Amazon Gift Card</p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/6o04w6y7785kfiu3ml-1766635738303.jpg" /></p>
<p><strong>Judging Criteria</strong></p>
<p>All eligible works will undergo evaluation based on their adherence to the theme, degree of completion, reception among players, and other relevant factors.</p>
<p><strong>Notes</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>To qualify for participation, you should include both hashtags #WutheringWaves and #WuWaFanart in your post and fill out the submission form.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Deleted posts will not be qualified for entitlement of rewards.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You can submit multiple entries and win multiple rewards. However, the same work published on different platforms will not count towards the rewards.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Entries listed below may be excluded from the judging process:</p>
</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Works not created in accordance with Wuthering Waves</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Works found to contain plagiarism or infringement of intellectual property rights</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Works submitted outside the event period</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Works created with the assistance of AI technology</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Works featuring extremely aggressive content, including but not limited to themes of pornography, violence, politics, or racism</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Works that have already been used for commercial purposes</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Works previously entered into other fan creation events</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Works deemed inappropriate by the judges</p>
</li>
</ul>
<ol start="5">
<li>
<p>Failure to reply to the official staff within 7 days from the date of notification will be considered a waiver of entitlement to the rewards.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>This event is open to submissions from all languages, as creators proficient in any language are eligible to compete for rewards. Entries differing only in language will be treated as equivalent works.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>By participating in the event, you grant KURO GAMES the right to freely republish your submitted content on the internet and social media platforms, with appropriate credit given to the creator. No additional notice will be provided prior to publication.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>This event is available solely to participants on the designated servers listed below: America, Europe, Asia, SEA, HMT(HK,MO,TW).</p>
</li>
</ol>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-25T11:34:05+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-25T11:34:05+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3929</id>
                    <title>V3.0 Wuthering Waves Battle Rush</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3929" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/p772voa7zur1qi3i1t-1766635247625.jpg" />Dear Rovers,</p>
<p>The Wuthering Waves Battle Rush is now live! Record and share your most exciting battle moments with the hashtags #WutheringWaves and #WuwaBattle on X (Twitter)/YouTube Shorts/TikTok to compete for a reward of Astrite x2,000 and a chance to get featured on our social media with direct credits! Other than these rewards, 10 extra winners will be selected to receive a $50 Amazon Gift Card.</p>
<p>Showcase your outstanding battle tactics in a condensed clip and share them with us!</p>
<p><strong>Content Requirement</strong></p>
<p>Create your own combat video featuring Wuthering Waves.</p>
<p>We require no limits to the characters, level, or scenes. All entries that feature your combat in Wuthering Waves are qualified to join the event and compete for rewards!</p>
<p><strong>How to Submit</strong></p>
<p>Post your work on X (Twitter)/YouTube Shorts/TikTok with both hashtags #WutheringWaves and #WuwaBattle included publicly.</p>
<p><strong>Submission Period</strong></p>
<p>2025/12/25 - 2026/01/22 (PT)</p>
<p><strong>Judging Criteria</strong></p>
<p>All eligible works will undergo evaluation based on their adherence to the theme, degree of completion, reception among players, and other relevant factors.</p>
<p><strong>Notes</strong></p>
<p>To qualify for participation, you should include both hashtags #WutheringWaves and #WuwaBattle in your post.</p>
<p>Deleted posts will not be qualified for entitlement of rewards.</p>
<p>You can submit multiple entries. However, the same work published on different platforms will not count towards the rewards.</p>
<p>Entries listed below may be excluded from the judging process:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Works not created in accordance with Wuthering Waves</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Works found to contain plagiarism or infringement of intellectual property rights</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Works submitted outside the event period</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Works created with the assistance of AI technology</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Works featuring extremely aggressive content, including but not limited to themes of pornography, violence, politics, or racism</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Works that have already been used for commercial purposes</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Works deemed inappropriate by the judges</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Failure to reply to the official staff within 7 days from the date of notification will be considered a waiver of entitlement to the rewards.</p>
<p>This event is open to submissions from all languages, as creators proficient in any language are eligible to compete for rewards. Entries differing only in language will be treated as equivalent works.</p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-25T11:33:23+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-25T11:33:23+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3920</id>
                    <title>Patch Notes for Version 3.0: We Who See the Stars</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3920" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/9sd49r45ei6hcd9vnm-1766581126248.png" /></p>
<p>Dear Rovers,</p>
<p>Thank you for your continued support. The following is a summary of content that will become available in Version 3.0: We Who See the Stars.</p>
<p><strong>[Maintenance Time &amp; Compensation Details]</strong></p>
<p><strong>✦Maintenance Time:</strong> <strong>2025-12-25 04:00 - 2025-12-25 11:00 (UTC+8)</strong></p>
<p><strong>✦Maintenance Compensation: Astrite x300, Crystal Solvent x2</strong></p>
<p><strong>✦Compensation Eligibility: Create a character and unlock the Mail feature before 2025-12-25 04:00 (UTC+8). The compensation will remain claimable until the next version update.</strong></p>
<p><em>In the event that the maintenance is extended, the dev team will issue a follow-up notice and adjust the compensation accordingly.</em></p>
<p><strong>✦Bug Fixes Compensation Astrite x300</strong></p>
<p><strong>✦Compensation Eligibility: Create a character and unlock the Mail feature before 2025-12-25 04:00 (UTC+8). The compensation will remain claimable until the next version update.</strong></p>
<p><strong>[Let&#39;s Go, to Startorch Academy!]</strong></p>
<p>Log in to the game after Version 3.0 goes live and claim the following rewards via in-game mail.</p>
<p><strong>✦Rewards:</strong> <strong>Radiant Tide x10, Crystal Solvent x10</strong></p>
<p><strong>✦Eligibility: Reach Union Level 2 and unlock the Mail feature. The rewards will remain claimable until the next version update.</strong></p>
<p><strong>[Version Update Details]</strong></p>
<h1>New Resonators</h1>
<p><strong>5-Star Resonator: Lynae (Spectro/Pistols)</strong></p>
<p>A Startorch Academy prep student whose head-turning, electric style hides an inner focus as explosive as a coiled spring.</p>
<h2>Combat Roles: Concerto Efficiency, Basic Attack DMG, DMG Amplification, Resonance Liberation DMG Amplification, Tune Rupture Response, Tune Strain Response, Tune Break Boost</h2>
<p><em>Obtainable through the [Undefined Spectrum] Featured Resonator Convene.</em></p>
<p><strong>5-Star Resonator: Mornye (Fusion/Broadblade)</strong></p>
<p>Mornye, a Spacetrek Collective Research Institute engineer and a Department of Exostrider Engineering professor at Startorch Academy.</p>
<p>Each step on her prosthetic legs carries her toward the stars of her dreams.</p>
<h2>Combat Roles: Support and Healer, DMG Amplification, Tune Rupture Response, Tune Strain Response, Off-Tune Buildup Rate</h2>
<p><em>Obtainable through the [Distant May the Starlights Be] Featured Resonator Convene.</em></p>
<h1>New Weapons</h1>
<p><strong>5-Star Weapon: Spectrum Blaster (Pistols)</strong></p>
<p>Prismatic light dances at her fingertips, arcs of color carving radiant trails.</p>
<p>Every rushing hue converges upon her aim, and at last, she reaches a sky where nothing lies beyond her sight.</p>
<p><em>Obtainable through the [Absolute Pulsation - Spectrum Blaster] Featured Weapon Convene.</em></p>
<p><strong>5-Star Weapon: Starfield Calibrator (Broadblade)</strong></p>
<p>Every pattern can be observed. Every phenomenon can be understood.</p>
<p>The ideal may lie light-years away, yet the path toward it rests within her own hands.</p>
<p><em>Obtainable through the [Absolute Pulsation - Starfield Calibrator] Featured Weapon Convene.</em></p>
<p><strong>Synth Armament Series (5-Star): Laser Shearer (Sword), Radiance Cleaver (Broadblade), Phasic Homogenizer (Pistols), Pulsation Bracer (Gauntlets), Boson Astrolabe (Rectifier)</strong></p>
<p><em>The weapons in the Synth Armament series are obtainable through Standard Weapon Convene.</em></p>
<h1>New Region</h1>
<p><strong>[Lahai-Roi]</strong></p>
<p><strong>Region includes: Starward Riseway, Fangspire Chasm, Bjartr Woods, Stagnant Run, Rebirth Uplands, Etching Plains, Startorch Academy, Mawburrow Desert, Giant&#39;s Gaze.</strong></p>
<p>A warm, humid underground haven deep beneath the Roya Frostlands. Following an ancient polar shift that made Lahai-Roi Solaris&#39;s new pole, the changing climate drove the surface-dwelling Roya to migrate below.</p>
<p>Long isolated, it became a refuge for extinct prehistoric life, which has since evolved into a unique and remarkably independent ecosystem.</p>
<p>**</p>
<h2>New Utility: Expedition Motorbike**</h2>
<p>The expedition motorbike is a lightweight, all-terrain vehicle co-developed by the Department of Exostrider Engineering and the Department of Voidmatters at Startorch Academy. You can summon the expedition motorbike or adjust the relevant settings via the Utility wheel. The motorbike cannot be summoned while in combat or when there is insufficient space.</p>
<p>[Motorbike Specs] When riding the expedition motorbike, you have access to features such as Acceleration, Boost, Drift, and Bounce Jump. While moving, a force field is deployed around the expedition motorbike, and the Resonator will be forced to dismount upon taking damage or being controlled after the force field is down.</p>
<p>[Motorbike Appearance] The Expedition Motorbike&#39;s appearance has three customizable areas: Left Fender, Right Fender, and Front/Rear. You can use the same Livery for all three areas, or use parts from different Liveries.</p>
<p>[Motorbike Expansion Modules] Complete Motorbike Modding Tasks to obtain Modding Points for specific modules, then spend those points to upgrade the Module to unlock more motorbike functions.</p>
<h1>New Echoes</h1>
<p>Hyvatia, Reactor Husk, Twin Nova: Nebulous Cannon, Twin Nova: Collapsar Blade, Flora Reindeer, Mining Reindeer, Ironhoof, Spacetrek Explorer, Sabercat Reaver, Sabercat Prowler, Frostbite Coleoid, Windlash Coleoid, Flora Drone, Mining Drone, Geospider S4, Zip Zap, Tremor Warrior</p>
<h2>New Tacet Discord Nest: Tacet Discord Nest - Lahai-Roi</h2>
<p><em>Two difficulty modes available: normal and difficult. A set number of Tacet Discords are available daily. Defeat them to claim the corresponding Echoes without spending Waveplates.</em></p>
<h2>New Sonata Effects: Pact of Neonlight Leap, Halo of Starry Radiance, Rite of Gilded Revelation</h2>
<p>Pact of Neonlight Leap (5pcs Set): Casting Outro Skill increases the ATK of the incoming Resonator who casts Intro Skill by 15%. Each point of Tune Break Boost the incoming Resonator has additionally increases their ATK by 0.3%, up to 15%. This effect lasts for 15s, or until the Resonator is switched out.</p>
<p>Halo of Starry Radiance (5pcs Set): When healing a Resonator in the team, every 1% of Off-Tune Buildup Rate grants a 0.2% ATK increase to all Resonators in the team for 4s, up to 25%. Effects of the same name cannot be stacked.</p>
<p>Rite of Gilded Revelation (5pcs Set): Dealing Basic Attack DMG increases Spectro DMG by 10% for 5s, stacking up to 3 times. With 3 stacks, casting Resonance Liberation grants 40% Basic Attack DMG Bonus.</p>
<h1>New Stories</h1>
<p><strong>Main Quest Chapter III: To the Stars Yet to Shine</strong></p>
<p>Both the fading frequencies and the old student ID point to that faraway place under the Roya Frostlands at the pole: Lahai-Roi.</p>
<p>The gateway to Lahai-Roi is now open. You will enter the Startorch Academy as a Synchronist. What burns beneath the frostlands is waiting for your return!</p>
<p><strong>Main Quest Chapter III Prologue: When the Unknown Thrums</strong></p>
<p><strong>Main Quest Chapter III Act I: What Burns Beneath Frostlands</strong></p>
<p><strong>Main Quest Chapter III Act II: Ode to the Second Sunrise</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Duration: Main Quest Chapter III Prologue: When the Unknown Thrums and Main Quest Chapter III Act I: What Burns Beneath Frostlands will become available when Version 3.0 goes live, while Main Quest Chapter III Act II: Ode to the Second Sunrise will become available on 2026-01-15 at 10:00 (server time).</li>
</ul>
<p><em>When Version 3.0 goes live, log in to the Terminal at the Resonance Nexus in Jinzhou during Main Quest Chapter I Act I &#34;First Resonance&#34; to unlock Main Quest Fast Track Event &#34;Next Stop: Lahai-Roi,&#34; which allows you early access to Main Quest Chapter III Prologue &#34;When the Unknown Thrums.&#34; Chapter III progress is saved separately from Chapter I progress and Chapter II progress. Taking on Chapter III early does not affect your progress in Chapter I or Chapter II.</em></p>
<p><em>For the optimal experience, we recommend completing Chapter II Segue &#34;Flowing Starlight in the Iris&#34; first before starting Chapter III.</em></p>
<p><strong>Exploration Quest: Where Light Takes Shape</strong></p>
<p><strong>Exploration Quest: No. 1 Biker</strong></p>
<p><strong>Exploration Quest: The Lost Melody</strong></p>
<h1>New Events &amp; Gameplay Features</h1>
<p><strong>[Special Events]</strong></p>
<p><strong>[Lahai-Roi Pioneers] Area Exploration Event</strong></p>
<p>Join the Lahai-Roi Pioneer Project launched by the Spacetrek Collective! Explore every corner of Lahai-Roi, uncover its wonders, and earn rewards along the way.</p>
<ul>
<li>Duration: After the Version 3.0 update</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>[Capturing Starlight] Photo Collection Event</strong></p>
<p>A total of 9 Chrono Traces are scattered throughout Lahai-Roi. Explore areas according to the clues and snap the correct photo or search the target location to complete Collection tasks and claim the rewards.</p>
<ul>
<li>Duration: After the Version 3.0 update</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>[Peaks of Prestige: Rekindled Duel] Echo Combat Event</strong></p>
<p>Summon special Echoes from &#34;Peaks of Prestige&#34; to build your own deck and engage in thrilling duels across Lahai-Roi.</p>
<ul>
<li>Duration: After the Version 3.0 update</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>[Beyond the Waves: Lahai-Roi] Featured Exploration Event</strong></p>
<p>Participate and upload your Adventure Logs to the Lollo courier truck to get various Adventure Packages!</p>
<ul>
<li>Duration: 2026-01-01 04:00 - 2026-01-19 03:59 (server time)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>[Startorch Racing] Leisure Event</strong></p>
<p>The new Startorch Racing Season is officially underway! Give it up for on-track thrills, roaring crowds, and enticing prizes! Hop on your beloved motorbike and sign up for the race now!</p>
<ul>
<li>Duration: 2026-01-15 04:00 - 2026-02-04 03:59 (server time)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>[Signs of a Silent Star] Leisure Event</strong></p>
<p>Deciphering scrambled WavesLine messages will reveal their true form and earn you rewards.</p>
<ul>
<li>Duration: 2026-01-22 04:00 - 2026-02-04 03:59 (server time)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>[Gifts of Freshers Week] 7-Day Login Event</strong></p>
<p>During the event, log in to claim the day&#39;s login rewards from the event page.</p>
<ul>
<li>Duration: Version 3.0 Update - 2026-02-04 03:59 (server time)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>[Collab Event]</strong></p>
<p><strong>Persona Sonic</strong></p>
<p>Themed collaboration event with Persona 5 Royal, Persona 3 Reload, and Sonic the Hedgehog. Complete event tasks to unlock Collab Liveries and development materials.</p>
<ul>
<li>Duration: Version 3.0 Update - 2026-02-04 03:59 (server time)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>[New Gameplay Features]</strong></p>
<p><strong>Doubled Pawns Matrix: Pilot (New High Difficulty Recurring Challenge)</strong></p>
<p>In the Spacetrek Collective&#39;s database, invisible offenses and defenses occur every day. Locate the malice deep inside the matrix, and delete it.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Duration: After Version 3.0 Update - Before Next Version Update Maintenance</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Eligibility: Achieve at least 24 Crests in one phase of the Tower of Adversity&#39;s Hazard Zone and reach at least 3,500 points in one phase of the Respawning Waters: Torrents in Whimpering Wastes after 3.0 is released.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Operation: Frontier Renewal (New Permanent Event)</strong></p>
<p>Lahai-Roi&#39;s route network, along with the Spacetrek Observatory that used to monitor its terrain, ecosystem, and climate, has been devastated by a Void Storm. It&#39;s time to rebuild them all!</p>
<p>Use rebuild materials gathered in Lahai-Roi to assist Dhalifa in restoring the Route Network and the Spacetrek Observatory.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Duration: After the Version 3.0 update</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Eligibility: Reach Union Level 8 and complete Tutorial Quest &#34;Operation: Frontier Renewal.&#34;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>Other New Content</h1>
<h2>&#34;Tactical Hologram: Synchronization&#34; Challenge: Dreamless</h2>
<h2>Phantom Echoes: Phantom: Twin Nova Collapsar Blade, Phantom: Twin Nova Nebulous Cannon, Phantom: Chop Chop</h2>
<h2>Sigil: Voyager of the World</h2>
<h2>Titles: Bathed in Pain, Calamity Ender</h2>
<h2>Expedition Motorbike Liveries: Carefree Rainbow, Student Abby!</h2>
<p><strong>[Adjustments and Optimizations]</strong></p>
<h1>Resonators &amp; Weapons</h1>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Combat Mechanics**</h2>
<p><strong>New combat mechanic: Tune Break</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Click on the Tune Break icon on a Resonator&#39;s Forte page for more details.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Your Resonators&#39; attacks build up enemies&#39; Off-Tune Level. Once the enemy&#39;s Off-Tune Level reaches the limit, they enter the Mistune state. During the enemy&#39;s Mistune state, your Resonators can unleash a powerful Tune Break, dealing additional damage. Landing a Tune Break resets the enemies&#39; Off-Tune Level. Within a period after being struck by Tune Break, the enemy&#39;s Off-Tune level cannot be built up again.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Skills**</h2>
<p><strong>New feature: Resonance Mode Switch</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>The Forte pages of certain Resonators now feature a Resonance Mode Switch icon. Click on the icon to switch between Resonance Modes and change the combat characteristics.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A Resonance Mode icon appears under each of the Skills that can be affected by a Resonance Mode Switch, to show the current Resonance Mode.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Click on the question mark beside the Resonance Mode Switch icon for more details.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>Features</h1>
<p>**</p>
<h2>WavesLine:**</h2>
<p><strong>New feature: WavesLine</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>WavesLine allows you to receive messages from other characters, Resonators, chat groups, or organizations.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You can accept some tasks and quests and receive rewards through WavesLine.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Click on the settings icon in the top right corner of the WavesLine screen and switch between Chat Bubble or Chat Background styles.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Map:**</h2>
<p><strong>New feature: Region Guide</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Click on the icon in the bottom left corner of the Map screen to access this feature, which displays region-specific gameplay features for all the currently available regions.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You can jump to a specific gameplay feature that has been unlocked through Region Guide or check the unlock conditions for a gameplay feature that remains locked.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Specific gameplay features in unlocked regions can be pinned. You can pin up to 2 gameplay features.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Map functionality optimizations</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Added an overview of rewards for completing certain challenges already marked on the Map.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Adjusted the Map icon view and selection priority to reduce overlapping.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Adjusted certain Map functions to resolve the issue of minor Map icons remaining on the Map screen, as well as other problems.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Gallery:**</h2>
<p>New section in Gallery&#39;s Sceneries: Record</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>As you explore Lahai-Roi, by locking on certain visual assets in your surroundings, you can trigger a brief description of the target, and capture the moment in the Record section of the Gallery&#39;s Sceneries.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Access this feature via Gallery &gt; Sceneries &gt; Record.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Reprise of Tides**</h2>
<p><strong>Upgraded [Reprise of Tides] Returnee Event</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>(Added) Reprise Journey: During the Reprise Journey, you can claim Reprise Gift rewards by completing set tasks. You can also purchase the Reprise Bounty Unlock to obtain more rewards.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>(Added) Support Resonators: During Reprise of Tides, Support Resonators are available to use if you meet their SOL-3 Phase requirements.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>(Added) Leveling Aid: During Reprise of Tides, to fast-track levelling up Resonators, you will enjoy access to locations that contain upgrade materials and recommended Echoes for Featured Resonators currently available for Convene.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>(Added) New Content Showcase: Visit this page to check Featured Events, the latest Main Quest, and currently available Resonators for Convene.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><em>For more details about the optimizations made to Reprise of Tides, please refer to the Returnee Event Upgrade Notice.</em></p>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Birthday System:**</h2>
<p><strong>Updated the Birthday system</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>New Startorch Academy-style 2026 Birthday gift.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Birthday Blessing Review. You&#39;ll be able to re-access the wishes sent to you by various Resonators.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>New Startorch Academy-style Birthday Blessing screen.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>If you did not log in within 7 days but did log in within 30 days of your birthday, the gift will still be sent to you, but now via WavesLine instead of mail, and the gift will be permanently available in your WavesLine.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><em>If you haven&#39;t unlocked WavesLine, the gift will be sent to your Backpack. Your Birthday gift will always be there for you.</em></p>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Projector:**</h2>
<p><strong>Optimized the functionality of Utility: Projector</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>You may project Echoes by equipping unlocked Echoes from the Gallery into the Projector via the Utility Wheel panel. Utility: Projector is no longer tied to the Main Echo equipped on the current Resonator.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Use Utility: Projector to call out the selection menu and choose the Echo to be projected. The Utility: Projector cannot be used to project more than one Echo.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Some areas in Lahai-Roi present puzzles that require special interactions. Use the Projector to create the appropriate Echo Projection to help your exploration.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>Leveling</h1>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Data Bank:**</h2>
<p><strong>Increased Data Bank&#39;s Max Level and adjusted some functions</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>The Data Bank&#39;s Max Level is increased to 30.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When the Databank Level reaches 25, new UI effects will become available for the Terminal on the Data Bank page.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When the Data Bank Level reaches 27, in addition to existing Enhanced Absorptions for COST 4 (Overlord Class/ Calamity Class) Echoes, Enhanced Absorption attempts will also apply to COST 1 (Common Class) and COST 3 (Elite Class) Echoes.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When the Data Bank Level reaches 30, the weekly Enhanced Absorption attempts for COST 4 (Overlord Class/ Calamity Class) Echoes will be increased to 20.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Purification and Separation:**</h2>
<p><strong>Made the Purification &amp; Separation system stack with double-drop events</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>When claiming rewards upon completing certain challenges, you can spend double Waveplates to claim double rewards. This feature is now also available during Bountiful Crescendo and Chord Cleansing.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When you choose to claim double rewards during the event period, if you have more than 2 double-drop claims remaining, you&#39;ll consume 2 claims to receive 4 times the rewards, and if you only have one claim left, you will consume 1 claim to receive triple rewards.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>Challenges, Puzzles, &amp; Events</h1>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Fantasies of the Thousand Gateways:**</h2>
<p><strong>Adjusted Fantasies of the Thousand Gateways</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Added a new method of obtaining Remnant Crystals. Each week, Fantasies of the Thousand Gateways provides 2 attempts to freely claim the first 2 rewards from Remnant Crystal without Waveplates. Free reward collections do not carry over to the next week. (※ A Waveplate-free attempt only provides one set of rewards.)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In each Fantasies of the Thousand Gateways challenge, the number of attempts allowed for claiming Remnant Crystals has been increased from 2 to 4.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Adjusted the method of claiming certain rewards (after interacting with the Remnant Crystal); to claim the rewarded Random Echo, you now select a Tacet Field on the page and obtain the corresponding Echo. You must clear the target Tacet Field challenge and claim its original reward before you can claim the same set of rewards again from the interface.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><em>The above adjustments to Fantasies of the Thousand Gateways will take effect on 2025-12-29 at 04:00 (server time), when the new cycle of this event goes live.</em></p>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Herald of New Tides:**</h2>
<p><strong>New event for new players: Herald of New Tides</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>New players who meet the requirements can participate in this event to unlock Support Resonators and include them in their teams for a better combat experience.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>During the event, increase your SOL3 Phase to unlock more Support Resonators and receive bonus rewards.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>During this event, to fast-track levelling up Resonators, you will enjoy access to locations that contain the upgrade materials and the recommended Echoes of the current Featured Resonators and New Voyage Resonators.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>UI</h1>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Event Interface:**</h2>
<p><strong>Display optimizations of the event interface</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Added a corner countdown timer to limited-time events when they are within 3 days of their closing time.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Added icons that show the various event types, along with their corresponding descriptions.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Added an icon to mark the important event(s) in the current version.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Adjusted the display of various event tags.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Login Screen**</h2>
<p><strong>Lahai-Roi-style login screen in Version 3.0</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Adjusted the visuals displayed on the login screen.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Adjusted the login music.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Replaced static visuals on the lineup interface with dynamic ones.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Adjusted the display and UI of the Announcement menu.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>Graphics &amp; Performance</h1>
<p><strong>Extended the availability of the Frame Generation option on mobile</strong></p>
<p>To enable the Frame Generation option, your device must meet one of the following requirements:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Dimensity 9400 or 9400+ (not including tablet computers equipped with 9400e or 9400)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Snapdragon 8 Gen 5</p>
</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Access the Frame Generation option via Settings &gt; Graphics &gt; Frame Generation.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Enable this option to increase the frame rate while running the game.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><em>For Dimensity 9400 or 9400+, you need to enable the Vulkan option first before enabling the Frame Generation option.</em></p>
<p><em>Please note that there is a frame rate limit on mobile devices produced by certain manufacturers.</em></p>
<p><strong>Adjusted Graphics settings</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Optimized the Special Effects Quality and Shadow Quality when the Graphics Quality is set to Ultra Performance, Performance, Balanced on some devices.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Widened the range of visuals affected by the LOD Bias option when enabled in the Graphics settings.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Due to variations in the in-game settings and system environment, enabling the option may occasionally cause performance issues, in-game glitches, and hardware-related issues. If you encounter issues, please try disabling the option. If the issue persists, please contact customer support for further assistance.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Added interactive effects to certain types of vegetation and sand in Lahai-Roi on PC.</li>
</ul>
<h1>Audio</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Improved the audio performance of cutscenes; added audio details that make a cutscene feel more well-rounded.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Adjusted the sound effects for when enemies take hits, to make them clearer and more distinguishable.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>Other</h1>
<h2>Game Assets Management</h2>
<p>Added Resource Download Options &amp; Resource Cleanup on Mobile</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Upon entering the game after a successful login on mobile, a resource download menu will pop up. You can choose between Full Resources and Basic Resources.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Select Full Resources to download all the available resources in one go. Or select Basic Resources to download only story resources for the early game.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>After officially entering the game, you can view details about resource download options via Settings &gt; Other &gt; Manage Game Assets, and the remaining resources may be downloaded in the background as you play the game.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Resource Cleanup allows you to delete the cutscenes that you have watched and are saved on your device. You can check the size of the saved cutscenes via Settings &gt; Other &gt; Resource Cleanup, and delete them as you see fit.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Adjusted the number of items from which you can select when you open a Pioneer Podcast Supply Pack in Version 3.0.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Optimized the descriptions of certain in-game settings and functions.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>[Bug Fixes]</strong></p>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Resonators &amp; Weapons**</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where some of the skill VFX might persist in certain domains after Resonator Qiuyuan finished casting Resonance Liberation &#34;Sundering Strike&#34; or was in the &#34;Inksplash of Mind&#34; state.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where the texts of some of Resonator Galbrena&#39;s Voicelines failed to display properly.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where Resonator Galbrena&#39;s character model on the &#34;Resonators - Resonance Chain&#34; screen behaved abnormally.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed a clipping issue that affected Resonator Augusta&#39;s character model on the &#34;Resonators - Overview&#34; screen.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where the model of Resonator Fleurdelys&#39; weapon behaved abnormally on mobile devices.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where certain player actions might cause Resonators Ciaccona and Chixia to move at an abnormal rate while using Heavy Attack to aim and shoot.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed a clipping issue that sometimes affected the hair of Resonator Carlotta&#39;s character model after switching to walking mode.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where after using Terminal Swap in certain circumstances, the Terminal displayed was not the one currently equipped.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue in the &#34;Fantasies of the Thousand Gateways&#34; event where Resonators Taoqi and Lumi were not listed on the Recommended page.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where the buff &#34;Increase DMG dealt through Poetic Essence&#34; was granted to non-Poetic Essence skills when the buff was triggered through Antithesis, Triplet, Perfect Rhyme on Resonator Youhu&#39;s Forte Circuit &#34;Poetic Essence.&#34;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>-Fixed an issue where the VFX for some weapons failed to display properly after a Resonator cast an Echo Skill to transform into the Echo.</p>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Enemies &amp; Echoes**</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where damage dealt by the &#34;Nightmare: Inferno Rider&#34; Echo Skill in Riding Mode did not match the DMG Multiplier shown in the description of the skill.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Adjusted the number of invincibility frames for some enemies after they respawn.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where the Trophy &#34;Follow the Map&#34; could not be obtained.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue in Co-op Mode where the Sigil displayed on the Player Info page failed to display properly.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where the icons of certain factions on the &#34;Gallery - Main Story - Main Quests&#34; screen were not correctly displayed.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where edits made in Echo Management failed to take effect under certain circumstances.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where in-game icons might flicker on PC devices equipped with AMD graphics cards and with the Frame Generation option enabled.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where the &#34;Tactical Hologram: Phantom Pain&#34; page flickered on some Android devices under certain settings.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where the game might become unresponsive at certain points on some Android devices.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Challenges, Puzzles, &amp; Events**</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fixed an issue in the &#34;Stranger Things in Honami&#34; event where the model of the NPC &#34;Polmes&#34; failed to display properly under certain circumstances.</li>
</ul>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Quests**</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where the group photo taken following the completion of Main Quest Segue &#34;Flowing Starlight in the Iris&#34; inside the Shashou Cafe, located in the Black Shores&#39; Chronorift Metropolis, might fail to display properly.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue in Side Quest &#34;Cerulean Echoes Adrift in the Winds&#34; where the Aetherfin challenge continued when all the energy had been consumed.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>**</p>
<h2>Environment**</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where interactions with certain objects in the &#34;Black Shores -Chronorift Metropolis&#34; area failed to perform normally.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where characters could move outside the bounds of the Map in certain parts of the &#34;Black Shores - Chronorift Metropolis - Shashou Cafe&#34; area.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where the models of certain objects in the &#34;Black Shores - Chronorift Metropolis &#34; area failed to perform normally on some Android devices.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where certain player actions could cause certain environment assets in the &#34;Rinascita - Septimont - Minos Sewers&#34; area to float in mid-air.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where certain above-ground models in some parts of the &#34;Rinascita - Septimont&#34; might fail to perform normally.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where the models of certain structures in the &#34;Rinascita - Avinoleum&#34; area failed to perform normally.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue in PS5 mode where the shadowing effects might fail to perform normally in the &#34;Rinascita - Averardo Vault - A Hidden Place&#34; area.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where the names displayed above some NPCs in the Black Shores did not match those shown in the corresponding dialogue text.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fixed an issue where certain environment assets in the &#34;Huanglong - Jinzhou&#34; area floated in mid-air.</p>
</li>
</ul>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-24T21:00:04+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-24T21:00:04+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3914</id>
                    <title>Wuthering Waves Fan Creation Event Winners Reveal</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3914" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/qe0nju92t3jety0tt5-1766631444739.png" /></p>
<p>Wuthering Waves Fan Creation Event &#34;To the City Set in Amber&#34; has concluded, and we want to express our heartfelt appreciation to all participants for their dedication and creativity in our fan art event.</p>
<p>Let&#39;s view the winning entries and their contributors!</p>
<p><strong>1st Place</strong></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/6sl15szv9l19wemguo-1766574383535.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/_toriumu">@_toriumu</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/js644zq9qefk4rda61-1766574520651.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/neelamayu_n">@neelamayu_n</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/kgts0cxgve11bjmdrc-1766574621155.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/fulfrui?__cft__%5B0%5D=AZYAk7iAArflMjxDbB_2v8qyCqWCltVxMNadEW16biV55_wFcwuh37qveszWC_zuUSf9q6CfUz-vE4JZ-g7FCfEG7C9Jl33HNY6qeo_Ghf_o-mOVZh_JrLCzHulnw60bfr8SNICjQP6YQWUV6apkvPu8MbYDbWBV1k2-yAA7QKX_Zw&amp;__tn__=,d-UC*F">@FulFrui</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/zjz0hc5l4ike0narh4-1766574832087.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/BrunoKerling">@BrunoKerling</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/qvvwmqqjay1mmicu7f-1766574994134.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/Yuelycia">@Yuelycia</a></p>
<p><strong>2nd Place</strong></p>
<p><strong><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/3yz647xenyypryr45t-1766628131054.jpg" /></strong></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/artdroiiid_ii">@artdroiiid_ii</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/3ha5kdli45ybrrpat2-1766628151506.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/linlinzhong1205?s=21&amp;t=byeTSS2PONchkpdtGxlG7g">@linlinzhong1205</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/rd2ghnuq8lm6ytr41v-1766628172945.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/Azipou_">@Azipou_</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/usd8mugjt8rc58wlxd-1766628187557.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/jonmaomao">@jonmaomao</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/1j7bmgv8ugppk84b6a-1766628203705.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/yirin3617">@yirin3617</a></p>
<p><strong>3rd Place</strong></p>
<p><strong><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/z5o7i5i89y5pcbexgj-1766628506081.jpg" /></strong></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/ossost07111/">@ossost07111</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/hedr6olee8pm0ezu9x-1766628568414.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/36smray">@36smray</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/itul3y97qrtjs0315i-1766628580920.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/namaconZ_006">@namaconZ_006</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/4kped4agheohefpff9-1766628594921.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/jvn_artwork">@jvn_artwork</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/0zc4ltf5feyiwkhclq-1766628609636.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/Bibimbub15">@Bibimbub15</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/ygw3mcm9munmmaii8t-1766628624493.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/oiro_ik">@oiro_ik</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/cdnrc91r220d5ddas9-1766629007542.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/yoshi_houndbell">@yoshi_houndbell</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/78jnxiolt05q38nyha-1766629023622.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/HanasawaHsu">@HanasawaHsu</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/rxujb5xdab6gymfymr-1766629034265.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/rena31415926">@rena31415926</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/8k5m3nzr2nh0tk2g1o-1766629047437.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/Fuwa2_om">@Fuwa2_om</a></p>
<p><strong>4th Place</strong></p>
<p><strong><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/uag0vgz4uwgb5z1zyr-1766630278773.jpg" /></strong></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/vankusman">@vankusman</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/gfwi82cqc0yucb08id-1766630303248.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/AgitoIsHere">@AgitoIsHere</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/dp83wtthfrjko28orm-1766630460151.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/chucky1000sun">@chucky1000sun</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/6m305wgu1qe8vthtc3-1766630478801.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/ElinaNoodles">@ElinaNoodles</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/oiq5rr08onooqvnyw3-1766630508944.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/Jelmul">@Jelmul</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/fj7sktvysp05fey4jk-1766630579915.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/yasukiart27_">@yasukiart27_</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/z1xjszhyblg5ekw02o-1766630597363.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/inc_moon">@inc_moon</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/yrxrr714gjtw2d4pcw-1766630611842.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/camunekoz">@camunekoz</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/yrsxm2pck9nibn9h18-1766630631857.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/koge_cha_n">@koge_cha_n</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/aajk35voauoaurzggb-1766630645427.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/zani_journey/">@zani_journey</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/7axfeas3jfmjk7wudt-1766630660511.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/HanTen_1O">@HanTen_1O</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/7yydo2tcjwf76jrket-1766630688134.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/PoanDan">@PoanDan</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/sys27zu1p12jayfsk6-1766630719776.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/yoru_shiki">@yoru_shiki</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/mt3liiqdjpi8ediz6j-1766630738930.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/ooC1iD7XwimLOou">@ooC1iD7XwimLOou</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/r1i9bh2znhn44d9a5j-1766630755887.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/songpyeon990/">@songpyeon990</a></p>
<p><strong>5th Place</strong></p>
<p><strong><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/uk1nscvv19u5779v0w-1766630907904.jpg" /></strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/zuo.mu.604593">@sagi_0116</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/qnfegx08zgh7v83yrw-1766630930636.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/brbubsh">@brbubsh</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/4j3zzgt5pcfqkl9bum-1766630952611.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/SenkaDraws">@SenkaDraws</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/zlreff63deyn5wfsqn-1766630988466.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/hodangdang_ok/">@hodangdang_ok</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/5zn1wjhun48tfmmrwj-1766631007027.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/PotatoKunai">@PotatoKunai</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/p6ctkpg3dldpsw473p-1766631057644.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/LeppiB">@LeppiB</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/5vhkkivxg5okup6yxa-1766631080119.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/morted14">@morted14</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/nziphp42sekwxfo3k4-1766631100593.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/Eien_001_">@Eien_001_</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/6tgvg8qzv698lhzdu3-1766631123845.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/stvviz">@stvviz</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/5ewshsazo3wy35w6yf-1766631141083.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/ArchionTurkey">@ArchionTurkey</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/5cz6k853v3vy7qr70b-1766631154498.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/LewdLily66">@LewdLily66</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/kffxnu0ea7eexlmikx-1766631177311.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/BeginningEgg">@BeginningEgg</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/drfcgehyfx5v0tkuxn-1766631195404.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/utim_utim">@utim_utim</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/7c7epy847x00t5ekkp-1766631212102.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/hyaui_kazuki">@hyaui_kazuki</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/ewrnxmhghmile2m78r-1766631228332.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/Rockwell_n1">@Rockwell_n1</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/r1vafni6muvfb7oody-1766631253745.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/mewutd/">@mewutd</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/wnssc3ei5fyt6w8n76-1766631272788.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/connectedskyy/">@connectedskyy</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/isoiqq11w64j9x9i4l-1766631289991.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/SOMoon0603/">@SOMoon0603</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/a3vmgol79p3j9heewl-1766631307181.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/Zenta_twt1">@Zenta_twt1</a></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766592000000/ywo49rlvk5x1tispjk-1766631324012.jpg" /></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/KiyoOtter">@KiyoOtter</a></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-24T18:54:26+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-24T18:54:26+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3879</id>
                    <title>Resonator Review | Woven Melodies—Ciaccona</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3879" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A wandering bard from Rinascita, Ciaccona. She sings not only for the Divinity, but also for the common folk.</p>
<p>She records stories along her journeys, turning them into songs that evoke laughter, emotion, and tears in both the storytellers and the audience.<img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/g8fwmr32oom2hfqccj-1766556431206.jpg" /></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/bg5q1lbi7eenaw5pzf-1766556497778.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/c213gh53s2d5x66907-1766556518846.jpg" /></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-24T14:09:06+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-24T14:09:06+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3863</id>
                    <title>[Absolute Pulsation] Featured Weapon Convene: Woodland Aria</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3863" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/6b13ngruxd8qlhqm3s-1766549470636.jpg" /></p>
<p>During the event, 5-Star Weapon: Woodland Aria, 4-Star Weapons: Relativistic Jet, Endless Collapse, and Undying Flame receive boosted drop rates!</p>
<h1>Duration</h1>
<p>Version 3.0 Update - 2026-01-15 09:59 (server time)</p>
<h1>Eligibility</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Reach Union Level 5.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Or complete the combat trial in First Resonance.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Or access Main Quest Fast Track Event and proceed with the Main Quest until you reach a certain point.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>Convene Rules</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>[Absolute Pulsation] is a Featured Weapon Convene event banner.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Use Forging Tide to convene. You are guaranteed at least one 4-Star or higher rarity Resonator or Weapon every 10 attempts.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The guarantee count is shared among all Featured Weapon Convene events and is carried over until a 5-Star Weapon is obtained.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The 5-Star Weapon you Convene is guaranteed to be Woodland Aria.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Featured Weapon Woodland Aria is exclusive to the Featured Weapon Convene and will not be available by other means once the event ends.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><em>For more details, please refer to the in-game Convene page.</em></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-24T12:11:25+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-24T12:11:25+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3862</id>
                    <title>[Through Verses and Rhythms] Featured Resonator Convene: Ciaccona</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3862" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/locuvxlktl1tr3zyj9-1766549404553.jpg" /></p>
<p>During the event, 5-Star Resonator: Ciaccona, 4-Star Resonators: Yangyang, Youhu, and Baizhi receive boosted drop rates!</p>
<h1>Duration</h1>
<p>Version 3.0 Update - 2026-01-15 09:59 (server time)</p>
<h1>Eligibility</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Reach Union Level 5.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Or complete the combat trial in First Resonance.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Or access Main Quest Fast Track Event and proceed with the Main Quest until you reach a certain point.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>Convene Rules</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>[Through Verses and Rhythms] is a Featured Resonator Convene event banner. Use Radiant Tide to convene. You are guaranteed at least one 4-Star or higher rarity Resonator or Weapon every 10 attempts.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The guarantee count is shared among all Featured Resonator Convene events and is carried over until a 5-Star Resonator is obtained.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Featured Resonator Ciaccona is exclusive to the [Through Verses and Rhythms] Featured Resonator Convene and will not be available by other means once the event ends.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Featured Resonator Ciaccona&#39;s Waveband will be simultaneously made available in the Afterglow Coral Store with a limit of 2 purchases, and it will be removed once the Convene event ends.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>During the event, all the Resonators who receive boosted drop rates will become available in Ascendant Aces as Trial Resonators. Complete their Ascendant Aces challenges to obtain rewards.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><em>For more details, please refer to the in-game Convene page.</em></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-24T12:10:23+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-24T12:10:23+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3861</id>
                    <title>[Absolute Pulsation] Featured Weapon Convene: Defier&#39;s Thorn</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3861" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/sjn9npj817v8d3dlqs-1766549320036.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/e4zwr9ofewmj9ezipi-1766549343282.jpg" /></p>
<p>During the event, 5-Star Weapon: Defier&#39;s Thorn, 4-Star Weapons: Relativistic Jet, Endless Collapse, and Undying Flame receive boosted drop rates!</p>
<h1>Duration</h1>
<p>Version 3.0 Update - 2026-01-15 09:59 (server time)</p>
<h1>Eligibility</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Reach Union Level 5.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Or complete the combat trial in First Resonance.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Or access Main Quest Fast Track Event and proceed with the Main Quest until you reach a certain point.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>Convene Rules</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>[Absolute Pulsation] is a Featured Weapon Convene event banner.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Use Forging Tide to convene. You are guaranteed at least one 4-Star or higher rarity Resonator or Weapon every 10 attempts.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The guarantee count is shared among all Featured Weapon Convene events and is carried over until a 5-Star Weapon is obtained.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The 5-Star Weapon you Convene is guaranteed to be Defier&#39;s Thorn.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Featured Weapon Defier&#39;s Thorn is exclusive to the Featured Weapon Convene and will not be available by other means once the event ends.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><em>For more details, please refer to the in-game Convene page.</em></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-24T12:09:32+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-24T12:09:32+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3860</id>
                    <title>[Dance in the Storm&#39;s Wake] Featured Resonator Convene: Cartethyia</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3860" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/h8x49a73jovhkvbr8m-1766549259256.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/33mmrynp4bpm7cl5z4-1766549273493.jpg" /></p>
<p>During the event, 5-Star Resonator: Cartethyia, 4-Star Resonators: Yangyang, Youhu, and Baizhi receive boosted drop rates!</p>
<h1>Duration</h1>
<p>Version 3.0 Update - 2026-01-15 09:59 (server time)</p>
<h1>Eligibility</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Reach Union Level 5.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Or complete the combat trial in First Resonance.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Or access Main Quest Fast Track Event and proceed with the Main Quest until you reach a certain point.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>Convene Rules</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>[Dance in the Storm&#39;s Wake] is a Featured Resonator Convene event banner. Use Radiant Tide to convene. You are guaranteed at least one 4-Star or higher rarity Resonator or Weapon every 10 attempts.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The guarantee count is shared among all Featured Resonator Convene events and is carried over until a 5-Star Resonator is obtained.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Featured Resonator Cartethyia is exclusive to the [Dance in the Storm&#39;s Wake] Featured Resonator Convene and will not be available by other means once the event ends.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Featured Resonator Cartethyia&#39;s Waveband will be simultaneously made available in the Afterglow Coral Store with a limit of 2 purchases, and it will be removed once the Convene event ends.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>During the event, all the Resonators who receive boosted drop rates will become available in Ascendant Aces as Trial Resonators. Complete their Ascendant Aces challenges to obtain rewards.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><em>For more details, please refer to the in-game Convene page.</em></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-24T12:08:12+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-24T12:08:12+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3859</id>
                    <title>[Absolute Pulsation] Featured Weapon Convene: Spectrum Blaster</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3859" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/p3vizxxxfi0b5zrbpm-1766549202039.jpg" /></p>
<p>During the event, 5-Star Weapon: Spectrum Blaster, 4-Star Weapons: Relativistic Jet, Endless Collapse, and Undying Flame receive boosted drop rates!</p>
<h1>Duration</h1>
<p>Version 3.0 Update - 2026-01-15 09:59 (server time)</p>
<h1>Eligibility</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Reach Union Level 5.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Or complete the combat trial in First Resonance.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Or access Main Quest Fast Track Event and proceed with the Main Quest until you reach a certain point.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>Convene Rules</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>[Absolute Pulsation] is a Featured Weapon Convene event banner.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Use Forging Tide to convene. You are guaranteed at least one 4-Star or higher rarity Resonator or Weapon every 10 attempts.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The guarantee count is shared among all Featured Weapon Convene events and is carried over until a 5-Star Weapon is obtained.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The 5-Star Weapon you Convene is guaranteed to be Spectrum Blaster.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Featured Weapon Spectrum Blaster is exclusive to the Featured Weapon Convene and will not be available by other means once the event ends.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><em>For more details, please refer to the in-game Convene page.</em></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-24T12:06:59+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-24T12:06:59+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3858</id>
                    <title>[Undefined Spectrum] Featured Resonator Convene: Lynae</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3858" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766505600000/4pcrkf6n4r7wvjp4gz-1766549125682.jpg" /></p>
<p>During the event, 5-Star Resonator: Lynae, 4-Star Resonators: Yangyang, Youhu, and Baizhi receive boosted drop rates!</p>
<h1>Duration</h1>
<p>Version 3.0 Update - 2026-01-15 09:59 (server time)</p>
<h1>Eligibility</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Reach Union Level 5.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Or complete the combat trial in First Resonance.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Or access Main Quest Fast Track Event and proceed with the Main Quest until you reach a certain point.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1>Convene Rules</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>[Undefined Spectrum] is a Featured Resonator Convene event banner. Use Radiant Tide to convene. You are guaranteed at least one 4-Star or higher rarity Resonator or Weapon every 10 attempts.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The guarantee count is shared among all Featured Resonator Convene events and is carried over until a 5-Star Resonator is obtained.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Featured Resonator Lynae is exclusive to the [Undefined Spectrum] Featured Resonator Convene and will not be available by other means once the event ends.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Featured Resonator Lynae&#39;s Waveband will be simultaneously made available in the Afterglow Coral Store with a limit of 2 purchases, and it will be removed once the Convene event ends.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>During the event, all the Resonators who receive boosted drop rates will become available in Ascendant Aces as Trial Resonators. Complete their Ascendant Aces challenges to obtain rewards.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><em>For more details, please refer to the in-game Convene page.</em></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-24T12:05:48+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-24T12:05:48+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3850</id>
                    <title>Resonator Review | Feathered Tempest—Cartethyia</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3850" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Cartethyia, the wandering knight who travels across Rinascita. Formerly known as the Blessed Maiden, the vessel of Divinity, and the Queen of Gale and Tide, she went by the name Fleurdelys. Now, she is simply a free and unfettered wandering knight.</p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766419200000/bxfskwv3px0zrjxdr5-1766470721868.jpg" /></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766419200000/ywrnk50ksu3mne7s8z-1766476885463.jpg" /></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766419200000/arkvd4lokufnc9x5og-1766470828261.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766419200000/kv4b3p3vtwyi2bagkp-1766470849617.jpg" /></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-23T14:21:23+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-23T14:21:23+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3843</id>
                    <title>Wuthering Waves Update Content | Version 3.0 &#34;We Who See the Stars&#34; Planned for Release on December 25th (UTC+8)</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3843" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Wuthering Waves Update Content | Version 3.0 &#34;We Who See the Stars&#34; Planned for Release on December 25th (UTC+8)</p>
<p>Here&#39;s the event calendar for Version 3.0. Check it out for a quick overview of the event schedule! <img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766332800000/86h1z00zh5e2btxegm-1766389137304.jpg" /></p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766332800000/2xm6l40hpb7mhboryq-1766389153083.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766332800000/qcrbzcy64apiav0nje-1766396898193.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766332800000/vue5qye9vls18bb0xi-1766389193512.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766332800000/gs19r3dvcbbc089rtz-1766389215911.jpg" /></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-22T15:40:33+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-22T15:40:33+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3842</id>
                    <title>Profile Reveal | Radiant Spectrum — Lynae</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3842" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Loading Data&gt;&gt;&gt;</p>
<h1>Lynae</h1>
<p>A Startorch Academy prep student whose head-turning, electric style hides an inner focus as explosive as a coiled spring.</p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/9c31b5kkx6t277ci1a-1766236339793.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/grkg8rv21d0v4rlq52-1766236795787.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/6b0n9yyxh7k17d7hby-1766236814209.gif" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/2zymzu97zjlen56cic-1766236831296.gif" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/f0k5w2p60yjadeuref-1766236849476.gif" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/35vx7jc3jhaqf8th0m-1766236867293.gif" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/1ebqlzwzuyknkbh431-1766236882739.gif" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/jxy1gj1xji9f5r86hq-1766236895554.gif" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/uqnhbpfkc99nikvtz3-1766236907958.jpg" /></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-20T21:21:55+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-20T21:21:55+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
                <entry>
                    <id>urn:article:3837</id>
                    <title>Post-Lament Anthropocene: Stars Intertwined | Lynae</title>
                    <link href="https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com/en/main/news/detail/3837" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/>
                    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>&#34;Don&#39;t blink... you&#39;ll miss the best part!&#34;— Lynae</p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/jpv6j1g1p1j7nburf1-1766164083702.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/tfu07u87f042gef0p7-1766164345781.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/f43lndffbk9a1l7ri8-1766164385603.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/jut5ja2c5hqhh8gxnx-1766164423930.jpg" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/ka2asgm3ynh60itr84-1766164444527.gif" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/zej7djvapbmevxdxox-1766164468408.gif" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/vgcvo0bln0srskihp6-1766164487886.gif" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/6onqlvxl870sp56ruh-1766164501396.gif" /><img alt="" src="https://hw-media-cdn-mingchao.kurogame.com/object/1766160000000/48xvdqtmr9g40ohi3l-1766164635783.jpg" /></p>]]></content>
                    <published>2025-12-20T01:17:37+00:00</published>
                    <updated>2025-12-20T01:17:37+00:00</updated>
                    <category term="Notice"/>
                    <author>
                        <name>Wuthering Waves</name>
                        <email>wutheringwaves_ensupport@kurogames.com</email>
                        <uri>https://wutheringwaves.kurogames.com</uri>
                    </author>
                </entry>
        
</feed>
